Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive, 1960-2004 (Bulk 1973-2000) MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence, 173084
  - Subseries D: Flyers, Press Releases and Mass-mailouts, 173087
    - "T", various; 185671 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - "U", various; 185672 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - "V", various; 185673 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - "W", various; 185674 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - "X", various; 185675 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - "Y", various; 185676 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Subseries E: Address Books, 173088
    Contains address books as well as business cards and loose addresses and envelopes. Folders are arranged alphabetically by title. Business cards are arranged alphabetically, but all other material is in no particular order.
    - Address Book, undated; 185677 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Address Book, undated; 185678 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Address Book- photocopies, undated; 185679 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Addresses- Columbia, undated; 185680 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Business Card, undated; 185681 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Loose Addresses, undated; 185682 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Loose Addresses, undated; 185683 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Empty Envelopes, various; 185684 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Empty Envelopes, various; 185685 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Empty Envelopes, various; 185686 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Various Letterhead and Stationery, undated; 185687 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Series II: Semiotext(e) Projects, 174637
  This series contains correspondence, documents, manuscripts, and publication and promotional material for the projects of the Semiotext(e) group. Subseries A holds material on the issues of the Semiotext(e) periodical, as well as conferences and events put on by the group. This subseries also contains materials relating to the Semiotext(e) anthologies that reprint work from the earlier issues. Subseries B contains material relating to the Foreign, Native, and Active Agents book series, while Subseries C contains more general administrative files for the Semiotext(e) group.
  - Subseries A: Issues and Conferences, 181285
    This subseries contains materials pertaining to the various issues of the Semiotext(e) magazine as well as conferences and events organized by the group. The issues and conferences are arranged chronologically. The three large unfinished projects--the Panic, Japan, and Flesh-Eating Technologies Issues--have been listed by approximate date range and are grouped together. Often there is significant overlap between issues and conferences, with one growing out of the other. In such cases, materials have been placed with the best fit. Among the materials you can expect to find correspondence; notes, clippings and visual source material; manuscripts; layouts; flyers; and press clippings. Materials for each issue or conference is alphabetical by folder description. Material belonging to unidentified projects is found in the last folders in the series.
    - Issue 1 "Alternatives in Semiotics": Correspondence and unbound copy, c.1974; 186353 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Issue 1 "Alternatives in Semiotics": Cover, c.1974; 186354 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Issue 1 "Alternatives in Semiotics": Flyer, c.1974; 186355 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Issue 1 "Alternatives in Semiotics": Forthcoming Issues, c.1974; 186356 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Issue 1 "Alternatives in Semiotics": Layout of manifest/ order form, c.1974; 186357 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Issue 1 "Alternatives in Semiotics": Copy of "Sub-stance" No.1, served as model for Semiotext(e), 1971; 186358 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Conference "The Two Saussures": Correspondence, 1974; 186362 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Conference "The Two Saussures": Flyer, 1974; 186359 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Conference "The Two Saussures": Lecture notes (S.L.), c.1974; 186360 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Conference "The Two Saussures": Copy of "Cahiers de Ferdinand de Saussure", undated; 186361 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Issue 2 "Les deux Saussure": Flyer, 1974; 186560 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Issue 2 "Les deux Saussure": Mechanical for cover image (artist Gil Eisner), 1974; 186561 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Conference "Schizo-Culture": Flyers, 1975; 186562 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Conference "Schizo-Culture": Participant List, 1975; 186563 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Conference "Schizo-Culture": Press, 1975; 186564 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Conference "Schizo-Culture": Schedule, 1975; 186565 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Conference "Schizo-Culture": Text- Ti Grace Atkinson, 1975; 186566 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Conference "Schizo-Culture": Text- Michel Foucault Roundtable, c.1975; 186567 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Conference "Schizo-Culture": Text- R.D. Laing and M. Foucault Panel, c.1975; 186568 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Conference "Schizo-Culture": Various texts and notes, c.1975; 186569 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Issue 5 "Bataille": Correspondence, visual material, texts, c.1976; 186570 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Issue 5 "Bataille": Flyer, c.1976; 186571 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Issue 5 "Bataille": Layout, c.1976; 186572 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Issue 5 "Bataille": Layout, c.1976; 186573 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Conference "In Honor of Emile Benveniste": Flyer, 1976; 186574 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Issue 6 "Anti-Oedipus": Correspondence, c.1977; 186575 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Issue 6 "Anti-Oedipus": Cover design, c.1977; 186576 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Issue 6 "Anti-Oedipus": Cover design and Semiotext(e) original typeface logo, c.1977; 186577 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Issue 6 "Anti-Oedipus": Flyer, 1976; 186578 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Issue 6 "Anti-Oedipus": Original photographs, c.1977; 186579 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Issue 6 "Anti-Oedipus": Text, c.1977; 186580 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Cover design (original), c.1978; 186581 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Cover design, c.1978; 186582 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Layout, c.1978; 186583 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Layout w/ misc. visual material, c.1978; 186584 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Preliminary formatting, c.1978; 186585 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Preliminary formatting, c.1978; 186586 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Proofreading copy, c.1978; 186587 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Text- John Cage, c.1978; 186588 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Visual material, c.1978; 186589 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Issue 7 "Nietzsche's Return": Visual material, c.1978; 186590 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Correspondence, c.1978; 186733 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Documents, c.1978; 186734 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Documents, c.1978; 186735 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Flyer, 1978; 186736 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Layout, c.1978; 186737 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Layout, c.1978; 186738 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Layout, c.1978; 186739 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Layout, c.1978; 186740 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Layout w/ misc. visual materials, c.1978; 186741 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Notes, c.1978; 186742 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Notes, c.1978; 186743 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Notes on the issue's reception (S.L.), c.1978; 186744 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Martine Barrat, c.1978; 186745 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- William Burroughs (incl. text for Polysexuality), c.1978-1980; 186746 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Andre Cadere, c.1978; 186747 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- John Cage, c.1978; 186748 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Richard Foreman, c.1978; 186749 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Allan Ginsburg incl. correspondence, c.1978; 186750 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Phillip Glass, c.1978; 186751 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Felix Guattari, c.1978; 186752 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Kenneth King, c.1978; 186753 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Jack Smith, c.1978; 186754 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Jack Smith, c.1978; 186755 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Jack Smith, c.1978; 186756 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- Robert Wilson, c.1978; 186757 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- various, c.1978; 186758 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Text- various, c.1978; 186759 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": "Texts to be worked upon", c.1978; 186760 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Visual material- Diane Arbus, c.1978; 186761 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Visual material- Christopher Knoles, c.1978; 186762 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Visual material, c.1978; 186763 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Visual material, c.1978; 186764 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Issue 8 "Schizo-Culture": Visual material w/ some layouts, c.1978; 186765 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - (unpublished) "Schizo-Culture II": Miscellaneous materials, c.1978; 186767 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - (unpublished) "Schizo-Culture II": Promotional collage by Diego Cortez, c.1978; 186768 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - (unpublished) "Schizo-Culture II": Text- J. Grotowski "Lindisfarne in Manhattan" transl. Jacques Chwatt, c.1977; 186769 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - (unpublished) "Schizo-Culture II": Text- J. Grotowski "Lindisfarne in Manhattan" transl. Jacques Chwatt, c.1977; 186770 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Conference "Nova Convention": Correspondence, schedule, c.1978; 186853 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Conference "Nova Convention": Flyer and brochure, c.1978; 186854 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Conference "Nova Convention": Flyer w/ notes on verso, c.1978; 186855 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Conference "Nova Convention": Press, c.1978; 186856 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Conference "Nova Convention": Press, c.1978; 186857 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Conference "Nova Convention": Press, c.1978; 186858 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Conference "Nova Convention": Text- Kathryn Bigelow, c.1978; 186859 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Special Issue "Loving Boys": Documents, c.1980; 186860 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Special Issue "Loving Boys": Documents, c.1980; 186861 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Special Issue "Loving Boys": Fan/Hate mail, c.1980; 186862 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Special Issue "Loving Boys": Layouts, c.1980; 186863 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Documents, c.1980; 187098 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Documents, Cinel, c.1980; 187099 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Flyer, c.1980; 187100 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Flyer incl Loving Boys, Polysexuality, c.1980; 187101 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187102 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187103 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187104 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187105 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187106 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187107 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187108 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187109 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187110 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Layout, c.1980; 187111 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Notes, c.1980; 187112 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Press kit and "Art sale (Anina)", c.1980; 187113 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Text, c.1980; 187114 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Text, c.1980; 187115 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Visual material- Walton Ford, c.1980; 187116 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Visual material, c.1980; 187117 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Visual material, c.1980; 187118 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Issue 9 "Autonomia": Visual material, c.1980; 187119 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - (unpublished) "Pasolini Issue": Correspondence, c.1980; 187132 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - (unpublished) "Pasolini Issue": Plan and texts, c.1980; 187133 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - (unpublished) "Pasolini Issue": Texts, c.1980; 187134 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Issue 10 "Polysexuality": Documents, c.1981; 187135 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Issue 10 "Polysexuality": Flyer, c.1981; 187136 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Issue 10 "Polysexuality": Layouts, visual material incl. cover photo, c.1981; 187137 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Issue 10 "Polysexuality": Miscellaneous file, c.1981; 187138 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Event "Polysexuality" at the Kitchen, c.1981; 187139 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - (unpublished) "Evangelical Issue" materials, c.1981; 187140 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Documents, c.1982; 187159 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Documents, c.1982; 187160 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Documents, c.1982; 187161 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Documents, c.1982; 187162 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Documents, Berlin 1980, c.1982; 187163 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Documents, Women's movement in West Germany, c.1982; 187164 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Layout plan, c.1982; 187165 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Layout, photos, plan, c.1982; 187166 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Layout, photos, c.1982; 187167 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Proofreading copy, c.1982; 187168 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Text- Originals, c.1982; 187169 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Text- Originals, c.1982; 187170 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Text- Originals, c.1982; 187171 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Text- for Translation, c.1982; 187172 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Text- Virilio/S.L. interview, c.1982; 187173 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Visual materials- "Final Part IV", c.1982; 187174 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Issue 11 "German Issue": Visual materials, c.1982; 187175 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Issue 12 "Oasis": Layout, c.1984; 187314 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Issue 12 "Oasis": Layout, c.1984; 187315 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Issue 12 "Oasis": Layout, c.1984; 187316 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Issue 12 "Oasis": Layout, c.1984; 187317 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Issue 12 "Oasis": Original prospectus "Nomadism", 1983; 187318 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Event "Cemnot3kct": Flyers and press release, c.1984; 187319 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Event "Cemnot3kct": Press, c.1984; 187320 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Event "Ultimatum II": Information package (Semiotexte participated), 1986; 187321 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Anthology "Semiotext(e)'s First Dirty Dozen": Proofreading copy, 1987; 187322 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Anthology "Semiotext(e)'s First Dirty Dozen": Proofreading copy, 1987; 187323 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Issue 13 "USA" materials, c.1987; 187400 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Issue 14 "SF": Cover design, 1989; 187401 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Issue 14 "SF": Documents, c.1989; 187402 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Issue 14 "SF": Table of Contents, annotated, c.1989; 187403 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Event "German Tour": Correspondence, c.1991; 187404 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Translation (German): Kathy Acker's "Hannibal Lecter", c.1991; 187405 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Issue 15 "Architecture" materials, c.1992; 187408 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Issue 16 "Radiotext(e)": Flyer, 1993; 187409 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Issue 17 "Canada": Press release, 1994; 187410 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Issue 17 "Canada": Proofreading copy, 1994; 187411 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Issue 17 "Canada": Proofreading copy, 1994; 187412 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Anthology "More & Less": Table of Contents, c.1995; 187420 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Anthology "More & Less": Texts, c.1995; 187421 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Anthology "More & Less": Texts, c.1995; 187422 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Anthology "More & Less": Texts, cover designs, c.1995; 187423 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Event "Chance": Budget, c.1996; 187430 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Event "Chance": Casino Contracts, 1996; 187431 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Event "Chance": Catalogue, 1996; 187432 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Event "Chance": Correspondence, c.1996; 187433 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Event "Chance": Flyers and brochures, 1996; 187434 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Event "Chance": Flyer and brochure layouts, c.1996; 187435 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Event "Chance": Fundraising, c.1996; 187436 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Event "Chance": Media List, c.1996; 187437 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Event "Chance": Mousepad, c.1996; 187438 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Event "Chance": Photos, 1996; 187439 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Event "Chance": Press, c.1996; 187475 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Event "Chance": Press, c.1996; 187476 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Event "Chance": Press mailout, c.1996; 187477 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Event "Chance": Registration forms, 1996; 187478 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Event "Chance": Scrapbook- Max Carmichael, 1997; 187479 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Event "Chance": Scrapbook- Diana Watson, 2000; 187480 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Event "Chance": SF Bands, c.1996; 187481 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Event "Chance": Slides- Julia Scher, 1996; 187482 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Event "Chance": Text- Baudrillard originals, c.1996; 187483 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Event "Chance": Text- Baudrillard French version, c.1996; 187484 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Event "Chance": Text- Baudrillard, c.1996; 187485 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Event "Chance": Text- Crocker Coulson, c.1996; 187486 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Event "Chance": Text- Jenniper Kabat, c.1996; 187487 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Event "Chance": Text- Chris Kraus, c.1996; 187488 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Event "Chance": Text- Sue [Spaid], c.1996; 187489 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Event "Chance": Text- Shirley Tse, c.1996; 187490 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Event "Chance": Text, c.1996; 187491 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Event "Chance": Tickets, 1996; 187492 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Anthology "More & Less 2": Flyer, c.1999; 187493 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Anthology "More & Less 2": Texts, c.1999; 187494 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Conference "Deleuze/Guattari On the Edge": Correspondence, c.1999; 187495 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Conference "Deleuze/Guattari On the Edge": Documents, c.1999; 187496 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Conference "Deleuze/Guattari On the Edge": Flyers, c.1999; 187497 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Conference "Deleuze/Guattari On the Edge": Texts, c.1999; 187498 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Conference "Deleuze/Guattari On the Edge": Texts, c.1999; 187499 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Conference "Deleuze/Guattari On the Edge": Texts, c.1999; 187500 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Conference "Deleuze/Guattari On the Edge": Texts, c.1999; 187501 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - (unpublished) "Audiotext(e) Issue": Proposal, 1999; 187623 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - (unpublished) "Mexico City Issue" materials, c.1999; 187624 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Anthology "More & Less 3" materials, c.2000; 187515 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Call for Submissions, 1980s; 187691 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Correspondence and other materials, 1980s; 187692 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Documents, 1970s-80s; 187693 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Documents, 1985-7; 187694 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Documents- Paranoia, 1980s; 187695 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Documents- Schizophrenia, 1980s; 187696 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Notes, 1980s; 187697 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187698 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187699 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187700 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1986; 187701 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, c.1987; 187702 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, c.1987; 187703 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, c.1987; 187704 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187705 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187706 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187707 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187708 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187709 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1987; 187710 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, c.1987; 187711 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1985; 187712 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1988; 187713 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Submissions, 1988; 187714 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Text- Bataille, 1980s; 187715 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Text- Celine, 1980s; 187716 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Text- Foucault, 1980s; 187717 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Text- Eldon Garnet, 1987; 187718 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Text- Eldon Garnet, 1988; 187719 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - (unpublished) "Panic Issue": Text- Kafka, 1980s; 187720 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Correspondence and submissions, 1990s; 187721 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Correspondence and submissions, 1990s; 187722 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Correspondence etc., 1990s; 187723 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Documents, 1990s; 187724 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Documents, 1990s; 187725 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Documents- Anthropology, 1990s; 187726 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Documents- Art, 1990s; 187727 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Documents- Language and Culture, 1990s; 187728 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Documents- Politics, 1990s; 187729 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Documents- Pop/Traditional Culture, 1990s; 187730 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Documents- "Traverses Japan", 1990s; 187731 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Grant, 1990s; 187732 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Japan trip, 1990s; 187733 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Japanese periodicals- "La Gaya Scienza" No.1, 1984; 187734 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Japanese periodicals- "Imago" Vol1.1, 1990; 187735 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - (unpublished) "Japan Issue": Japanese periodicals- "Wave" #19 Cyber City Issue, 1990; 187736 (Box 15, Folder 15)